Adam Haviv

ashaviv27@gmail.com

L 050-818-1126

github.com/ashvv1

ttps://www.adamhaviv.com

Profile

Profile

More than two years of experience working on professional and personal projects. Fast learning and

initiative-taking autodidact with English as a first language.

Has experience in planning, prototyping, and developing a product from the ground up. Very passionate about learning and creating. Looking for a Full Stack, Front End or Back End Developer position which will allow me to utilize my relevant experience as well as grow as a developer.

Technical Knowledge/Experience

Databases: MongoDB, Firestore, mySQL

In linkedin.com/in/adam-haviv-84bb17225/

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript,
 React.js, Next.js, jQuery, Svelte
- DevOps/Workflow: Docker, GitHub, Jira, Jenkins, EC2, ECR, Netlify, Heroku
- Cloud: AWS (EC2), Firebase, Mongo Atlas
- Web3: Solidity, Web3 Integrations Back-End: Node,JS, Express, PHP
- Testing: Jenkins, Mocha

Professional Experience

Software Developer, Cambium LTD, April 2023 - Present

Developing a wide variety of projects including automation and custom websites as part of a team or individually.
 *Was previously in charge of project coordination and development of the product of a foreign client.

Soft Skills: Flexibility, Willingness to learn new technologies from my peers, problem solving.

Technologies: Typescript, React, Svelte, PHP, HTML, SCSS, MUI, Zustand

FullStack Developer (Intern), Minerva XR, August 2022 - April 2023

Developing a wide variety of projects including automation and custom websites as part of a team or individually.
 *Was previously in charge of project coordination and development of the product of a foreign client.

Soft Skills: Team work, prototyping, debugging, planning and

implementation of LMS; managed AWS services (EC2, ECR) and updated

Docker images; produced true to Figma frontend for LMS, frequent code

Technologies: Firestore/Firebase, React.js, Node.js

Python Insructor, Cambium LTD, October 2022 - June 2023 • Teaching 10th graders Python while following a strict syllabus intended to

prepare students for Army service in cyber units.

Soft Skills: Relaying complicated concepts in a simplified manner to high schoolstudents while developing their coding and problem-solving skills.

Education

SV College, January 2022 - June 2022

FullStack Development Program

- Fullstack Development Program
 Focus on MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node)
- CodeCademy, October 2021 Janury 2022

Online FullStack Course

- Certificate of completion (Front-End Development)
- Certificate of completion (Front End
 Certificate of completion (JavaScript)

Languages

• Hebrew - Fluent

English - Native